== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Leonard:)Hey, Raj, I read a couple
guys in your department
(Leonard:)may have discovered a new
planet in our solar system?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I heard about that.
(Sheldon:)Why didn't you
discover it?
(Raj:)Because instead of being
in the telescope room,
(Raj:)I was busy making you guys
homemade jam for the holidays.
(Sheldon:)Well, you be sure
to let us know
(Sheldon:)when you win the Nobel
Prize for boysenberry.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
Hey, bud.
(Leonard:)Ready to play when you are.
(Howard:)Yeah, um, in a minute.
(Howard:)I actually need
to tell you guys something.
If it's "thank you"
for the homemade jam
(Raj:)you got in December,
congratulations,
(Raj:)you're the
first one.
(Leonard:)What's going on?
(Howard:)I'm, uh...
(Howard:)uh, gonna be a father.
(Raj:)That's so amazing.
What? Congratulations.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no.
Why "oh, no"?
(Sheldon:)Because this changes everything.
(Sheldon:)What about comic book night?
(Sheldon:)Uh, what about playing
games together?